Hello everyone, welcome back to to this another new tutorial series. So today going to explore for how to update the data in the MySQL table using for the update statement. Okay, so first of all here, the update statement in the first grade used to modify the existing records in a table. Okay, it allows us to change the values of the specific column in one or no based on the certain condition. Okay, so first of all, you are.
I can simply update the single column in the SQL. So now we can hear update for the company table having a required. So just follow. So first of all, I can just open the company table. So just here, I can select then step on here is the company. Okay, so you can see here, this is the company.
The basic statement for the starting process. So now we can select and we can see here, this is the company table record. So first on the ID name is then the address and also for the calendar. Okay, so here first use the first example for suppose like we can update for the address for the customer and now.
Here, great for this statement update for.
Here the salary where it is okay, so now we can do another new query and once again, use the update statement and update here, this is the.
Any and use the set for the salary in this way and now here I can just use while dot ID is equal to j okay.
So now here perfectly different and here I can just build the semicolon.
And now right the value of the state. So now the step I can use for the set the seller okay.
So now here declare the set salary is equal to and here we want to execute because you can see the.
Perfectly affected so here use for another ID. So here I can use for the ID one and now I can just use for.
Now you can see here this on.
Please 25,000 and this is the company for other the 20,000 okay.
So this the 20,000 for the.
This one okay so now just click and hit by so first of all here select and I can execute and you can see here this all row is completely updated.
So now just going for the first example and here now just looking for select and execute and you can see here the completely update.
So previous salary range is 20,000 and will update the 40,000 and the ID is one and secondly from here I did see and previous one here the range the amount of range for the salary.
I hope you perfectly understand it.
Next step here use for the another example so here I can modify for all the address and the salary column.
For the company table so if you don't need to use the.
Well close and update query for.
As now so here you can see here this that this information on the California Texas so now we're going to get here now I can choose your all addresses for the Texas okay.
So now just go here first of all here I can use for the update the company said the address okay.
So define for that this is a just go again and consider create a single quotation and now here type these.
This is the texture so here completely different and here also create for another test for another component of the seller okay so use for here completely for the seller is equal to so now here inside for the seller is.
Now for this one okay so here I can start that 80 okay so 80,000 and now you can see perfectly created this and there I can just select and completely update the company maybe.
And here just select and execute you can see here completely full is perfectly update now I can just check for and then completely update in this statement companion now select and execute and you can see the all added for the Texas and all salary in here okay.
So I hope you perfectly understand it and here completely working for this okay so here in this session is completely done and then have the whole view of the updating data in the post web SQL or some practical examples I hope you perfectly understand this session so thank you for watching and happy coding okay.